

## FRONTEND DEVELOPER

## VOLODYMYR TSIMAR

My GitHub: (github.com/tsimar)

## **CONTACT DETAILS**

Tel: 794 774 445

E-mail: vtsimar@gmail.com

87-100, Toruń

### **SKILLS**

- Java basics
- MySql
- Hibernate
- Spring
- HTM & CSS
- GIT
- JavaScript
- React
- Bootstrap
- API
- Axios
- · Strict mode
- Highly developed interpersonal skills
- Knowledge of Photoshop
- Analytical thinking

## **LANGUAGES**

- English A2 and keep learning
- Polish B2/C1
- Ukrainian fluent

Since 2020 I have been learning how to program in Java and JavaScript. I took part in two professionals bootcamps to improve my skills and learn from the best polish Mentors.

IT industry was always my passion, so now I am looking for a job, where I can develop my qualifications and be a valuable asset to the company.

#### **EDUCATION**

**FUTURE COLLARS (03.2022 - 07.2022)** 

• FRONTEND DEVELOPER BOOTCAMP (210 h)

SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT ACADEMY (09.2020-07.2021)

• JAVA FROM SCRATCH BOOTCAMP (360 h)

#### KHMELNITSKY NATIONAL UNIVERSITY (1998-2003)

 HIGHER ENGINEERING, UKRAINE ENG., METAL-MACHINE TOOL MECHANIC

## **EMPLOYMENT HISTORY**

TECHNOLOGY PROCESSING - UNI-KAT COMPANY (03.2022-NOW) GRABOWIEC, POLAND

- CREATING A PROGRAM FOR CNC MACHINING
- SETTING THE EXECUTION ORDER
- MANAGING A TEAM OF FOUR

# CNC PROGRAMMER - EDELWEJS COMPANY (07.2015-07.2016) UKRAINE

- CREATING A PROGRAM FOR KNITTING MACHINES,
- DESIGN OF SWEATER MODELS,
- TECHNOLOGICAL PROCESS CALCULATION

#### **AFTER WORK**

- Active recreation with family (bicycle, walking)
- IT
- Travels

I agree to the processing of personal data provided in this document for realising the recruitment process pursuant to the Personal Data Protection Act of 10 May 2018 (Journal of Laws 2018, item 1000) and in agreement with Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (General Data Protection Regulation).